Niall Moore Rosfaraghan Ferbane, Co. Offaly Phone: (086) 0806866

Email: moore.nialls@gmail.com

Personal Profile: I am a multi- skilled mechanic with good all round technical and mechanical expertise. I am a productive team player who is capable of working to deadlines and targets, self-motivated, organised and able to multi-task. Having nine experience of running my own business, I have gained great organisational skills, interpersonal skills and general skills that can be used in a variety of jobs across a number of industries.

Employment History

2010 - 2014 Athlone Communications, Castlepark, Ballinasloe, Co. Roscommon.

Position: Self Employed.

Duties:

- Established and marketed own business.
- Providing an effective and efficient customer service.
- Sales and fitting of Tracking systems, hands free car kits and taxi meters to customers vehicles.
- Adhering to Health and Safety Regulations.

2005 - 2010 A2B Cabs, Castlepark, Ballinasloe.

Position: Self Employed Taxi Driver.

Duties:

- Providing an effective customer service.
- Assist passengers with any luggage or cargo they may have.
- Collect fares from passengers.
- Maintain the cleanliness of the car.
- Ensure the car is operating properly.

2003 - 2005 Advance Pitstop, Athlone, Co. Westmeath.

Position: Tyre Fitter.

Duties:

- Providing an effective customer service.
- Visual inspection of client's tyres, exhausts, shocks and brakes.
- Advise customers on follow through action as required.
- Daily mix of cars and large vehicle and HGVS.
- 24 hour breakdown service 7days per week.
- Selling and promoting the Pitstop brands and products.

2000 - 2003 Murphy Truck Centre, Ballymount, Dublin 24

Position: Motor Mechanic.

Duties:

• 24 Hour Accident and Emergency Recovery.

- Ability to repair customer's vehicles.
- Take instructions from the garage foreman.

• Ability to diagnose faults on vehicles using specialist diagnostic equipment and to then successfully repair or replace defective parts.

1996 - 1999 New York.

Position: General Labourer.

Duties:

Working on a building site belonging to NYPD.

1995 - 1996 Banagher Concrete, Banagher, Co. Offaly.

Position: Mechanic.

1994 - 1995 JJ Healion, Arden Road, Tullamore, Co. Offaly.

Position: Mechanic.

1990 - 1994 Liam Young, Castledaly, Moate, Co. Westmeath.

Position: 4 Year Mechanic Apprenticeship.

Educational History

1986 – 1989 Ferbane Vocational School, Ferbane, Co. Offaly.

1978 – 1986 Ferbane National School

Further Training

Present Code Institute Diploma in Software Development

Credited by Edinburgh Napier University

September 2016 LWETB, Garrycastle, Athlone, Co. Westmeath.

Dreamweaver CS6 Webdesign (Day-Class)

Febuary 2016 LWETB, Garrycastle, Athlone, Co. Westmeath.

Dreamweaver CS6 Webdesign (Night-Class)

September 2015 LWETB, Garrycastle, Athlone, Co. Westmeath.

Social Media Day Coarse

April 2015 Birr Job Club, Brendan St, Birr, Co. Offaly.

Course: Job Seeking Skills.

2010 Cygnus Automotive.

Course: Certified as a Taxi Meter Fitter.

2010 FÁS Training Centre, Garrycastle, Athlone, Co. Westmeath.

Course: Computers & Business Accounts.

1990 – 1994 Athlone Regional College.
Course: Apprentice Motor Mechanic.

Hobbies

I enjoy Fishing, Snooker, GAA Sports and Darts.

Additional Information

Date of Birth: 03 March 1974

I hold a Full Clean Drivers Licence and I am a Van Owner.

Referees

References available upon request.